perfectaudience.com 2018-06-19

# Privacy Policy | Perfect Audience

_Last updated July 27, 2012_

Perfect Audience ("Perfect Audience," "we" or "us") produced this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to the online privacy of Internet users. This document describes Perfect Audience' privacy practices as they pertain to our corporate website and any customer extranet (the "Site") and our real time advertising service (the "Service") and how we collect and use consumer data. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies and websites not under the control of Perfect Audience or to individuals that Perfect Audience does not employ or manage. 

### What information is collected by Perfect Audience?

#### We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information

Personally identifiable information ("PII") is information that can be used to identify an individual user, for example, a person's name, home address, email address, or phone number. Perfect Audience does not generally collect PII from Internet users in connection with the Service. However, if someone sends PII to us in an email or voluntarily provides PII to us in any other way, we will receive and store such information.

Users should also be aware that advertisements provided by the Service may direct users to the website of third party advertisers, and such third party advertisers are not subject to this privacy policy. Therefore, users should carefully review the privacy policies of the websites they visit to assess the security of any PII they disclose.

#### We collect Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Data

In order to customize the online user experience and provide our clients with useful statistics and analysis regarding their websites and advertisements, Perfect Audience may collect certain anonymous information (i.e., information that is not linked to PII), including but not limited to a usage information, transaction information, IP addresses, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, number of clicks, mouse position, scroll position and time on page. We may use such information to analyze trends, administer the Site and the Service, customize the advertising and content users may see, track users' movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

#### Information Collected From Other Websites and Do Not Track Policy

Through cookies we place on your browser or device, we may collect information about your online activity after you leave our Services. Just like any other usage information we collect, this information allows us to improve the Services and customize your online experience, and otherwise as described in this policy. Your browser may offer you a “Do Not Track” option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services (including behavioral advertising services) that you do not wish such operators to track certain of your online activities over time and/or across different websites. Our Services do not support Do Not Track requests at this time, which means that we collect information about your online activity both while you are using the Services and after you leave our Services. Remember that this is just our Do Not Track policy, and we can’t and don’t make any promises about how third parties react when you set this signal on your browser.

### How does Perfect Audience use the information it collects?

The non-personally identifiable data that Perfect Audience collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements to people across the different websites they visit. The data is also used to predict responses to advertisements, to help determine which ads perform best.

If a user voluntarily provides Perfect Audience with PII in an email or by completing an online form, we will use that PII only to contact such user to respond to such user's inquiry.

### Does Perfect Audience share the information that it collects with anyone?

Perfect Audience may share the aggregate information it collects with advertisers, publishers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties.

We do not rent or sell PII to anyone. We share PII only in the following limited circumstances: Only with a user's consent, Perfect Audience may share such user's PII with third parties with such user's consent, for example, when the user agrees to our sharing of the user's information with other third parties for purposes of responding to the user's inquiry. We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services (e.g., without imitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Service's features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties may have access to PII but only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. In addition to the above, there is also the possibility that Perfect Audience, or part(s) of the company, may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company. If that's the case, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to information we have previously collected. Finally, we may release PII when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a court order or to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials, enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements, or protect the rights, property or safety of Perfect Audience, our employees, users, or others.

Most websites employ "cookies," small packets of data, which may include an anonymousunique identifier that are sent to a user's browser from a website's computer and stored on the user's computer's hard drive. The website placing the cookie on the user's computer can then recognize the computer when the user navigates the website at a later time.

If you'd like to opt-out from having Perfect Audience collect your Non-PII in connection with our Platform, please [click here](http://pixel.prfct.co/coo). If you'd like to opt-out from having our partners collect your Non-PII on behalf of Perfect Audience, please [click here](http://ib.adnxs.com/optout). When you opt out, we will place an opt-out cookie on your computer. The opt-out cookie tells us not to collect your Non-PII to help us tailor our Clients' online advertisement campaigns. Please note that if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.

### What security measures does Perfect Audience use to protect the information that it collects?

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorizedalteration, disclosure or destruction of data. This includes the necessary physical, electronic and managerial procedures to protect data integrity, access and use. This also includes, but is not limited to the use of encryption. Any data that is stored on Perfect Audience' servers is treated as confidential and is not generally available to the public. Perfect Audience has an internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, limiting access only to those employees who we reasonably believe need to know such information for the purpose of performing their jobs. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect PII, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Please send questions about security to tech at Perfect Audience.com.

### What about third party sites?

Perfect Audience' Site or Service may permit users to link to other websites on the Internet, including those of third party advertisers, and other websites may contain links to the this Site. These other websites are not under Perfect Audience' control and Perfect Audience is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

### What about children's privacy?

Perfect Audience is very sensitive to the issue of children's privacy. Perfect Audience' Site and Service are neither developed for, nor directed at, children. If you believe your child has provided Perfect Audience with personally identifiable data and you would like to have the data removed, please contact us at tech at Perfect Audience.com.

### How is this privacy policy updated?

Perfect Audience may find it necessary to update this privacy policy from time to time. We will conspicuously note any material changes and post the changes in this privacy policy on our Site. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently.

### How do I contact Perfect Audience?

To inquire about privacy concerns, please contact Perfect Audience by mail at the address below or email us at info at Perfect Audience.com.
